Guide to the Paper Tiger Television Archive, ca. 1981-2014 MSS.276
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Oversize Series V: Posters and Maps
  - Certs - subway ad / poster, Undated (Folder 20 Right)
  - Defense Committee against Fascism - poster, Undated (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - "Diary of a Shirtwaist Striker" poster, Undated (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - European Media Arts Festival / University TV poster, Undated (Folder 26)
  - "Ewa: My Grandmothers Story" poster, Undated (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Institute for Democratic Socialism - poster, 1980 (Folder 21 Right)
  - Iran Contra posters, Undated (Folder 27)
  - "It's Possible" - Palestinian and Israeli art exhibit poster, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Map of New York, Undated (Flat-file 5B)
  - Map of the forty primary trade areas, 1980 (Folder 22 Right)
  - Maps of New York, NY, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - "Nuclear Winter: Changing our Way of Thinking" poster, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - "Stop Bush's War in the Middle East" poster, c. 1991 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - "The Talking Band in Work-Song" poster, Undated (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Tats Cru - calendar, 2000 (Folder 23 Right)
  - University Gallery - "In the Shadow of..." poster, 1985 (Folder 29)
  - Van Gogh TV poster, 1991 (Folder 25)
  - "Vote the Big Bombs Out of the Big Apple" poster, Undated (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - "Women Get AIDS Too" [subway poster], Undated (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - World map - from FedEx, Undated (Folder 24)
- Oversize Series VI: Photographs
  This series contains the oversize material from Series VI: Photographs.
  - Mounted photos, Undated (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Mounted photos, Undated (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Mounted photos, Undated (Box 38, Folder 29)
- Series XI: 2016 Accretion of Paper Tiger Audio and Visual Recordings, 1983-2003; 70 Linear Feet in 68 record cartons, 2 media boxes, and 2 full manuscript boxes.
  This accretion includes video and audio cassette tapes, CDs, and Betamax masters from broadcasts from 1992 to 2003 by Paper Tiger TV. Subject matter includes events in South America (mining disasters), 9/11 coverage, and interviews, as well as coverage of pop culture, politics, and performance art.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Donated by Julie Ludwig, Paper Tiger Television. The accession number associated with this gift is 2016.021.
  Arrangement
  Materials have not been arranged by an archivist.
  - Fenced Out, Undated; cuid21362; 3 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 164, Cassette cuid21362, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records cuid21362)
    Format: 3/4" Umatic, Duration: 30 min.
  - Herb KO's Corporate Sports - Dub Master, Undated; cuid21460 (Box 142, Cassette 234)
    Original format: 3/4" U-matic, Duration: 28 minutes
  - Spoken By An Actor: Censorship and Cinema in Ireland - Dub Master, 1995-03-27; cuid21461 (Box 166, Cassette 237)
    Original format: 3/4" U-matic, Duration: 29 minutes
  - Spoken By An Actor: Censorship and Cinema in Ireland - Dub, 1995-03-27; cuid21462 (Box 166, Cassette 237)
  - Spoken By An Actor: Censorship and Cinema in Ireland, 1995-03-27; cuid21463 (Box 166, Cassette 237c)
  - A Cry For Freedom and Democracy, 1994; cuid21464 (Box 166, Cassette 254)
  - A Cry For Freedom and Democracy - Dub, 1994; cuid21465 (Box 166, Cassette 254, Box 142)
  - Street Sheet - Dub Master, 1995-06-30; cuid21466 (Box 166, Cassette 239)
  - Street Sheet, 1995-06-30; cuid21467 (Box 166, Cassette 239b)
    Original format: 3/4" U-matic, 28 minutes
  - Street Sheet - Dub, 1995-06-30; cuid21468 (Box 166, Cassette 239)
  - Wired For Action: Women's Organizations Jammin The Media, 1994-02-04; cuid21469 (Box 166, Cassette 242, Cassette 242a, Cassette 242b)
    Original format: 3/4" U-matic, Duration: 26 Minutes 40 Seconds
  - Shredded Hopes - 1994 Mexican Elections - Dub, 1995-09-24; cuid21470 (Box 166, Cassette 255, Box 165)
  - A Cry For Freedom and Democracy - Dub Master, 1994; cuid21471 (Box 142, Cassette 254)
    Original format: 3/4" U-matic, Duration: 28 Minutes
  - The Power Elite at the Bohemian Grove - Dub, End Dated; cuid21472 (Box 142, U-matic 246)
  - Shredded Hopes - 1994 Mexican Elections - Dub Master, 1995-09-24; cuid21473 (Box 165, Cassette 255)
  - Super Barrio Mexico 1994, Undated; cuid21474 (Box 165, Cassette 257)
    Original format: 3/4" U-matic, Duration: 28 Minutes 15 Seconds
  - Super Barrio Mexico 1994 - Dub, Undated; cuid21475 (Box 165, Cassette 257)
  - Dan Hallin Unmasks Jacobo Zabludosky - Dub Master, 1995; cuid21476 (Box 165, Cassette 258)
  - Dan Hallin Unmasks Jacobo Zabludosky - Dub, 1995; cuid21477 (Box 165, Cassette 258)
  - The Scroll Green Chimney Rough Cut, Unknown; cuid21478 (Box 165, Cassette 258)
    Original format: 3/4" U-matic, Duration: Unknown
  - Episode 256: Married With Children: Part II On Motherhood, 2009-11-17; cuid21479; 2 videocassettes (u-matic) Dub and Dub master (Box 165, Media 256)
  - Episode 201: Operation Dissidence, Gulf Crisis TV Project, Unknown; cuid21482 (Box 143, Cassette 201c, Cassette 201b)
  - Episode 202: Getting Out of the Sand Trap, Gulf Crisis TV Project, Unknown; cuid21483 (Box 143, Cassette 202/203B, Cassette 202/203)
    Original format: 3/4" U-matic, Duration: 58 Minutes
  - Episode 72: Flo Kennedy on US Press on South Africa - Dub Master, Unknown; cuid21484 (Box 143, Cassette 72b, Box 15, Cassette 72a)
  - Episode 72: Flo Kennedy on US Press on South Africa, cuid21485 (Box 143, Cassette 72a)
  - Episode 200: War, Oil, and Power, Gulf Crisis TV Project - Dub Master, Unknown; cuid21486 (Box 143, Cassette 200, Cassette 200/201A)
  - Episode 205: Manufacturing the Enemy, Gulf Crisis TV Project - Dub Master, 1990; cuid21487 (Box 144, Cassette 205a)
    Original format: 3/4" U-matic, Duration: 30 Minutes 15 Seconds
  - Episode 209: War on the Home Front, Gulf Crisis TV Project, Unkown; cuid21488 (Box 144, Cassette 209b, Cassette 209)
  - International Working Women's Day - Dub Master, 1990; cuid21489 (Box 154, Cassette 175)
    Original format: 3/4" U-matic Duration: Unknown
  - Episode 323: PTTV Reads PTTV - Dub Master, Unknown; cuid21498 (Box 155, Cassette 323)
    Original format: 3/4" U-matic, Duration: 48 Minutes
  - Episode 204: News World Order, Gulf Crisis TV Project - Dub Master, 1990; cuid21500 (Box 155, Cassette 204a)
    Original format: 3/4" U-matic, Duration: 29 Minutes 22 Seconds
  - Episode 183: Intervention Into A Field of Dreams - Dub Master, 1990; cuid21502 (Box 155, Cassette 183A)
    Original format: 3/4" U-matic, Duration: 30 Minutes 33 Seconds
  - Episode 204: News World Order, Gulf Crisis TV Project, 1990; cuid21501 (Box 155, Cassette 204d, Cassette 204)
- Series XII. August 2016 Accretion, 1988-2009; 14.5 linear feet in 14 record cartons and 5 manuscript boxes
  - Episode 8: Teresa Costa Reads Biker Lifestyles, undated; cuid4679; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) Dub Master (Box 148, Media 8, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4679)
    TRT: 27 Minutes 20 Seconds
  - Episode 32: Muriel Dimen Reads Cosmo, 1983; cuid4680; 1 videocassettes (minidv) (Box 146, Media 32, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4680)
    Duration: 29 Minutes 42 Seconds
  - Episode 34: Tom Weinberg Reads Wall Street Journal, 1982; cuid4681; 1 videocassettes (minidv) (Box 146, Media 34, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4681)
    Duration: 29 Minutes 27 Seconds
  - Episode 34: Tom Weinberg Reads Wall Street Journal, 1982-04-12; cuid4681; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) Dub Master (Box 148, Media 34, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4681)
    Duration: 28 Minutes 11 Seconds
  - Episode 41: Elayne Rapping Reads Romance Novels, undated; cuid4682 (Box 148, Media 41b, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4682)
  - Episode 43: Sandinista TV Part 2, undated; cuid4683; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 148, Media 43, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4683)
    Duration: Unknown
  - Episode 56: Neil Smith Reads USA Today, undated; cuid4684; 2 videocassettes (u-matic) Dub Master [56c] and Dub [56] (Box 146, Media 56, Box 148, Media 56c, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4684)
    Duration: 29 Minutes
  - Episode 66: Video Art Special, undated; cuid4685; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) Dub Masters (Box 148, Media 66, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4685)
    Duration: 28 Minutes
  - Episode 68: How Nations Televise Each Other, undated; cuid4686; 3 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 148, Media 68, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4686)
    Duration: 28 Minutes 51 Seconds
  - Episode 72: Flo Kennedy on US Press on South Africa, undated; cuid4687; 5 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 146, Media 72, Box 15, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4687)
    Duration: 26 Minutes
  - Episode 74: Youth and the Media: Escape from Tom & Jerry, undated; cuid4688 (Box 146, Cassette 74, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records cuid4688)
    Original format: MiniDV, Duration: 29 Minutes 29 Seconds
  - Episode 74: Youth and the Media: Escape from Tom & Jerry, undated; cuid4688; 2 videocassettes (minidv); 2 videocassettes (u-matic) Dub Master (Box 148, Media 74, Box 146, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4688)
    Duration: 29 Minutes 29 Seconds
  - Episode 77: Hal Fischer Reads American Photographer, undated; cuid4689; 2 videocassettes (u-matic) Master and Dub (Box 148, Media ID: 316d, 77, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4689)
    Original format: 3/4" U-matic, Duration: 29 Minutes 58 Seconds
  - Episode 79: Columbia Students Divestment Struggle, undated; cuid4690; 1 videocassettes (minidv) (Box 146, Cassette 79, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4690)
    Original format: MiniDV, Duration: 29 Minutes 58 Seconds
  - Episode 79: Columbia Students Divestment Blockade, undated; cuid4690; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) Dub Master; 1 videocassettes (minidv) (Box 148, Media 79, Box 146, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4690)
    Duration: 29 Minutes 58 Seconds
  - Episode 80: Doudou Dienne on the New World Information Order, undated; cuid4691; 4 videocassettes (u-matic) duplicates (Box 146, Media 80, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4691)
    Duration: 31 Minutes 36 Seconds
  - Episode 87: Noam Chomsky Reads The New York Times: Central America In the Paper of Record, 1985; cuid4692; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 166, Media 87, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4692)
    Duration: 40 Minutes 06 Seconds
  - Episode 88: Noam Chomsky Reads The New York Times: "Seeking Peace In the Middle East", 1986; cuid4693; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 147, Media 88, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4693)
    Duration: 30 Minutes 09 Seconds
  - Episode 96: Nidia Bustos on MECATE: How Campesinos are Creating Theatre and Art in Revolutionary Nicaragua, 1986; cuid4694; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 147, Media 96, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4694)
    Duration: 32 Minutes 20 Seconds
  - Episode 99: Leonard Siegal Reads Aviation Week: Paper Tiger Takes to the Wild Blue Yonder, 1986; cuid4695; 2 videocassettes (u-matic) Dubs (Box 166, Media 99, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4695)
  - Episode 103: Michele Mattelart Reads The Chilean Press Avant Coup: "Everyday It Gets Harder to Be a Good Housewife", 1986; cuid4696; 3 videocassettes (u-matic) Duplicates (Box 147, Media 103, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4696)
    Duration: 28 Minutes 44 Seconds
  - Episode 106: Ed Herman and The Famous Pope Plot: Who Dunnit?, 1986; cuid4697; 2 videocassettes (u-matic) Duplicates (Box 166, Media 106, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4697)
    Duration: 29 Minutes 09 Seconds
  - Episode 108: Under Siege: Palestinians in the U.S. Media, 1986; cuid4698; 5 videocassettes (u-matic) Duplicates (Box 147, Media 108, 107/108, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4698)
    Duration: 58 Minutes 06 Seconds
    Scope and Contents
    Five tapes that contain Under Siege, with one tape also containing Vernon Walters: Portrait of a Terrorist (Episode 107).
  - Episode 109: Michael Chanan on Reuters: From Carrier Pigeons to Orbiting Birds, 1987; cuid4699; 3 videocassettes (u-matic) Masters and/or dubs (Box 145, Media 109, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4699)
    Duration: 28 Minutes 5 Seconds
  - Episode 114: Thulani Davis Asks Why Howard Beach?: Racial Violence and the Media, 1987-01-21; cuid4700; 2 videocassettes (u-matic) masters and/or dubs (Box 145, Media 114, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4700)
    Duration: 30 Minutes
  - Episode 118: PTTV Invades "Amerika", 1987; cuid4701 (Box 145, Media 118, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4701)
    Duration: 29 Minutes 6 Seconds
  - Episode 126: Donna Haraway Reads The National Geographic on Primates, 1987; cuid4702; 2 videocassettes (u-matic) masters and/or dubs (Box 145, Media 126, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4702)
    Duration: 27 Minutes
  - Episode 129: "It Takes A Tough Ad Agency to Make a Tender Chicken:" Kathleen Hulser Debones the Poultry Industry, 1987; cuid4703; 4 videocassettes (u-matic) masters and/or dubs (Box 145, Media 129, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4703)
    Duration: 29 Minutes 53 Seconds
  - Episode 133: Red Ink: Rebecca Zurier Reads The Masses, 1987; cuid4704; 2 videocassettes (u-matic) masters and/or dubs (Box 145, Media 133, Box 146, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4704)
  - Episode 134: Herb Shiller Smashes the Crash, 1987; cuid4705; 4 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 149, Media 134, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4705)
  - Episode 139: Fred Landis Digests Selecciones, undated; cuid4706; 5 videocassettes (u-matic) masters and/or dubs (Box 149, Media 139, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4706)
  - Episode 147: Gloria House Reads: The Detroit Free Press, 1988; cuid4707; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) Dub Master (Box 151, Media 147, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4707)
  - Episode 152: CBS Tries the New York Three (NY3): Racist Lies on Prime Time TV, 1988, cuid4708; 3 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 157, Media 152, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4708)
  - Episode 155: Felt Evidence: Investigating Reproductive Technologies, 1989; cuid4709; 3 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 151, Media 155, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4709)
  - Episode 156: Transformer AIDS, 1988; cuid4710; 7 videocassettes (u-matic) masters and/or dubs (Box 152, Media 156, Box 158, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4710)
    Duration: 30 Minutes 44 Seconds
  - Episode 158: Desperately Seeking Reality: Herb Schiller Reads Trash TV, 1991-04-19; cuid4711; 8 videocassettes (u-matic) masters and/or dubs (Box 152, Media 158, 159, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4711)
    Duration: 31 Minutes 19 Seconds
  - Episode 159: Terry Odendahl's Glamour Workout, 1989, cuid4712 (Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4712)
  - Episode 161: Just Say Yes: Kathryn High Looks At Pharmaceutical Advertisements, 1989; cuid4713; 3 videocassettes (u-matic) masters and/or duplicates (Box 152, Media 161, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4713)
    Duration: 28 Minutes 55 Seconds
  - Episode 163: Fred Landis Reads The Washington Times: The Dark Side of the Moonies, 1989; cuid4714; 2 videocassettes (u-matic) masters and/or dubs (Box 153, Media 163, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4714)
    Duration: 29 Minutes 48 Seconds
  - Episode 166: Television Across Borders with Michael Silverman, 1989; cuid4715; 3 videocassettes (u-matic) masters and/or dubs (Box 153, Media 166, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4715)
    Duration: 26 Minutes 25 Seconds
  - Episode 167: How History Was Wounded: An Exclusive Report on Taiwanese Media, 1990; cuid4716; 6 videocassettes (u-matic) masters and/or dubs (Box 153, Media 167, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4716)
  - Episode 168: From Woodstock To Tiananmen Square: Ted Koppel's Long March, 1989; cuid4717; 3 videocassettes (u-matic) masters and/or dubs (Box 153, Media 168, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4717)
    Duration: 26 Minutes 57 Seconds
  - Episode 175: Notes On Zimbabwe, 1990; cuid4718 (Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4718)
  - Episode 183: Intervention Into A Field of Dreams, 1990; cuid4719; 4 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 14, Media 183, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4719)
  - Episode 184: The Road To Mississippi: "Reclaiming Our History" by the Through Our Eyes Video History Project, 1990; cuid4720; 2 videocassettes (u-matic) masters and dubs (Box 154, Media 184, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4720)
  - Episode 191: Operation Unjust Cause: Robt. Knight & P.T.T.V Look At The Illegal Invasion Of Panama, undated; cuid4721; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) Dub Master (Box 149, Media 191b, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4721)
  - Episode 195: Operation Storm the Media, undated; cuid4722; 4 videocassettes (u-matic) Duplicates (Box 146, Media 196, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4722)
    Duration: 30 Minutes 58 Seconds
  - Episode 196/197: Mutiny On the Corporate Sponsorship, Part I and Part II, 1991; cuid4723; 7 videocassettes (u-matic) A mix of Part 1, Part 2, and Part 1 & 2 (Box 154, Media 196, 196/197, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4723)
  - Episode 200: War, Oil, and Power, Gulf Crisis TV Project, 1990; cuid4725; 5 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 143, Media 200/201, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4725)
  - Episode 201: Operation Dissidence, Gulf Crisis TV Project, 1990; cuid4726; 2 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 155, Media 201, Box 15, Cassette 201, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4726)
  - Episode 202: Getting Out of the Sand Trap, Gulf Crisis TV Project, 1990; cuid4727; 4 videocassettes (u-matic) Duplicates (Box 155, Media 202, Box 15, Media 202/203B, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4727)
  - Episode 203: Bring the Troops Home!, Gulf Crisis TV Project, 1990; cuid4728; 3 videocassettes (u-matic) Duplicates (Box 155, Media 203, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4728)
  - Episode 204: News World Order, Gulf Crisis TV Project, 1990; cuid4729; 3 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 14, Media 204, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4729)
  - Episode 205: Manufacturing the Enemy, Gulf Crisis TV Project, 1990; cuid4730; 5 videocassettes (u-matic) masters and duplicates (Box 144, Media 205, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4730)
    Duration: 30 Minutes 15 Seconds
  - Episode 206: Lines in the Sand, Gulf Crisis TV Project, 1990; cuid4731; 3 videocassettes (u-matic) masters & duplicates (Box 144, Media 206b, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4731)
  - Episode 207: Global Dissent, Gulf Crisis TV Project, 1990; cuid4732; 3 videocassettes (u-matic) masters and duplicates (Box 137, Media 207, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4732)
  - Episode 208: Just Say No!, Gulf Crisis TV Project, 1990; cuid4733; 4 videocassettes (u-matic) masters and duplicates (Box 137, Media 208, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4733)
  - Episode 209: War on the Home Front, Gulf Crisis TV Project, 1990; cuid4734; 4 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 16, Media 209, Box 137, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4734)
  - Episode 225: Operation Class War, undated; cuid4735; 5 videocassettes (u-matic) masters and duplicates (Box 145, Media 225, Box 146, Box 150, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4735)
  - Episode 248: The Media Blanks on Healthcare Reform, undated; cuid4736; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) Dub master (Box 149, Media 248, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4736)
    Duration: 30 Seconds
  - Episode 250: Dis-Function: A Case of Healthcare Blues, undated; cuid4737; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) Dub Master (Box 149, Media 250, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4737)
  - Episode 265: Narrowcasting - The Rise of the Christian Right, undated; cuid4738; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) Dub master (Box 149, Media 265, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4738)
    Duration: 29 Minutes 4
  - Episode 273: Putting the Demo Back Into Democracy, undated; cuid4739; 12 videocassettes (u-matic) masters and duplicates (Box 150, Media 273, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4739)
    Duration: 1 Hour 56 Seconds
  - Episode 282: Freeing the Media, Part I, 1997; cuid4740 (Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4740)
  - Episode 283: Freeing the Media, Part II, 1997; cuid4741; 2 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 138, Media 283, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4741)
  - Episode 289: Showdown in Seattle: Seattle Prelude, Part I, 1999; cuid4742; 2 videocassettes (u-matic) masters and duplicates (Box 138, Media 289, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4742)
  - Episode 290: Showdown in Seattle: People Unite, Police Riot, Part II, 1999; cuid4743; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 138, Media 290, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4743)
  - Episode 291: Showdown in Seattle: Occupied Seattle, Part III, 1999; cuid4744 (Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4744)
  - Episode 292: Showdown in Seattle: Unwilling Captives, Part IV, 1999; cuid4745 (Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4745)
  - Episode 293: Showdown in Seattle: What Democracy Looks Like, Part V, 1999; cuid4746; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 138, Media 293, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4746)
  - Episode 294: Showdown in Seattle, 1 Hour Version, 1999; cuid4746 (Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4747)
  - Episode 323: Paper Tiger Reads Paper Tiger Television, undated; cuid4748; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 14, Media 323, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid4748)
- Series XIV: Archived Websites, September 2007-ongoing; 4 websites in 4 archived websites.
  Accruals
  New site crawls are accrued annually.
  Appraisal
  Robots.txt (a piece of code designed to limit crawler activity within a website) was ignored with the permission of the content owner. Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of http://papertiger.org/ in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567. Videos are inconsistently captured.
  Paper Tiger Television's website was first collected in 2007, documenting the organization's 25th anniversary. From 2009-2015, the website was captured more consistently, and contains information on their many projects and video series, such as the Paper Tiger Reads Working Women, Surveilling Surveillance, Urban Environmentalism: DIY Living Green, Gentrification in Sunset Park, Military Myths, production on the Peace Pentagon, Public Spaces, Exposing Deception, social movements, Detroit, fast Food workers strike, and El Taller Latino Americano. The website also contained information with descriptions of their historical programs and information on their weekly Wednesday broadcasts. Their blog contained descriptions of their programs, dating back to 2007 as well as events listings and some behind the scenes information. Video topics included art, community gardens, democracy and dissent, DIY and grassroots media, feminism, education, environment, events, free speech and censorship, science and technology, globalization, health, immigration, labor, LGTBQIA+, media criticism, peace and conflict, politics, pop culture, public space, race and class, science and technology, social movements, urban politics, women, consumerism and capitalism, and youth. In circa 2016-2017, the website redesigned to highlight the Paper Tiger archives (both images and video) and their more recent work dating until 2021. They also were a frequent collaborator with Deep Dish Television, on projects related to Mumia Abu-Jamal and organizing against "white nationalism, neoliberalism, patriarchy, and colonialism" after the election of President Donald Trump.
- Physical Digital Media (Box Shared Fales 074)